[{"answer": "Oh, you just don't know.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "How have you avoided becoming Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "I guess we're just clever in that way.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "Ladies, how have you managed to avoid ever doing an interview together?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "Nobody has ever asked us, Piers.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "And we wanted to stay friends, you know?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "I DM you all the time.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "Oh, you're in love with him?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, it's really fun.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "How -- sitting here together, how do you feel about doing a joint interview?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "We did an interview in England together.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Oh, you did?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 61, "question": "I loved it when you asked Hugh Hefner's girlfriend, 23, Hugh Hefner, 83, and what did she see in him?", "qSentId": 60}, {"answer": "Twenty-three goes into 83 more than 83 goes into 23.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "What did you make of that?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "You think so?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Does anyone care, do you think?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Is that what it is, good genes?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "Oh, my God, since I was 20.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "You have not exposed your face to the sun in how long?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "That's because I'm at my computer writing all the time.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Oh, no, no, no, no.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "I mean, have you had any real cataclysmic fallings out?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "And he didn't like you.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Which one was that?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "He was number three, right?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Well, I used to write and Joan used to illustrate.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What were you like together when you were young sisters?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I guess I did.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "And is that why you sort of developed the creative writing?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, our parents were very, very different from each other.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "What were you -- what were your parents like?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "Hence the five husbands.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "Were you?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "... very much.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "... is the way to put it, right?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "That is the right way 'round.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Is that -- is that the wrong way -- that's the right way around, right?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "Yes, I do, actually.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "And do you remember when Jackie went out with Marlon Brando?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Yes, well...", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "You and Marlon?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "... a certain temporary nature to the relationship that I don't think Joan would like you to convey.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Can you tell that I'm a writer?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What, for me?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "And such a nice, sweet, down-to-earth person.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "Paul Newman?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, I was very young, but I would skulk around these parties and watch people.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Who would your choice be?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "... he was such a bad ass.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "Because he was huge, right?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, that was a clip from your 1994 workout video.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "What am I doing, putting my arm up?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What, do the splits?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "No, I decided not to do them, yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Didn't you do the splits?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Well, no, I don't think so, because I don't -- first of all, I think that staying -- trying to look young is ridiculous.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Because the pressure is so unbearable, isn't it?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "I mean, cut to the -- have either of you two ladies ever succumbed to the scalpel?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "Because we're needle-phobic.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "Why have you been able to resist it when so many others have fallen by the wayside?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, I am, and she is, and our mother was.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Are you really?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "Well...", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 441, "question": "I look at you and I see healthy vitality, you know?", "qSentId": 440}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "You're sort of a get-up-and-go ladies, aren't you?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I don't put anything on my face at all.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "Because you just -- because you shave, first of all.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Well, how have I got good skin?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "ORGAN: No.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "You had Botox?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I guess.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "I mean, that was the movie really that propelled you into super stardom, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "Yes, somebody asked if he read my books.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 553, "question": "And what did he say to (inaudible)?", "qSentId": 552}, {"answer": "No idea at all.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Did you ever think it was going to be that huge?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "Well, I look like her.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 593, "question": "I mean, how like Alexis have you been over the years?", "qSentId": 592}, {"answer": "Not that much.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Do you flare up like that?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Do you think I do?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "She's a Gemini.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "Have you two ever had a fight like what we just saw?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "You've never rolled around on the floor?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Probably, to be honest.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Us rolling on the floor?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "And then I cut off all the buttons off all her clothes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "No, she -- I can't remember -- one of us jumped on the other one's back once when we were very, very young, and I think it was I who jumped on your back or you jumped on mine?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "Well, that's what I mean.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "How can you ever be friendly with anyone again after that?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "OAN COLLINS: I don't think it's ever been a friendship.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 647, "question": "Is there any way back for this friendship, do you think?", "qSentId": 646}, {"answer": "Well, this is for you.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Why haven't they given me one?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "And it says \"that sounds like a challenge.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Oh, it is?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "So stay tuned.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 676, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 675}, {"answer": "Could be.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "OAN COLLINS: I'm not allowed -- I'm not allowed -- I'm not allowed.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "Have we got a little scoop there?", "qSentId": 683}, {"answer": "It's been on Twitter, darling.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "Is \"Dynasty\" coming back?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "I can't say.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Yeah, but is it properly coming back?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't be talking about it if I wasn't.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 695, "question": "Are you going to be reprising?", "qSentId": 694}, {"answer": "You tell us.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Does sex get better with age, do you think?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "The classic gong buster (ph) material.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "I know, it's great, isn't it?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "How much of all the stuff that you write about have you actually partaken in?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 735, "question": "Seriously?", "qSentId": 734}, {"answer": "Well, I was a wild child.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "It's all based on your experience?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 759, "question": "A thousand?", "qSentId": 758}, {"answer": "You can sort of express yourself, and also I wanted to get a few followers because so when I have a book out, because I'm writing a book -- but it's not a novel.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 775, "question": "Why do you like it?", "qSentId": 774}, {"answer": "JoanCollinsOBE.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 786, "question": "What is your address?", "qSentId": 785}, {"answer": "JackieJCollins.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 791, "question": "And what is your address?", "qSentId": 790}, {"answer": "If I can -- if I can correct you, yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "What was mine?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "ORGAN: So all of you have been tarred with what could be a good brush, or a potentially irritating brush.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 858, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 857}, {"answer": "There is nothing bad about being compared to awesome actors.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Is that all good?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it's terrifying.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Does it put huge pressure on you when you get this label, you are the next huge superstar and they name somebody you should be like?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "I don't know, I mean, I feel I'm very new to it still.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 874, "question": "Is it all it's cracked up to be?", "qSentId": 873}, {"answer": "Well, I think especially your publicist and people who you -- work on your team.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 879, "question": "What is -- what is that -- what is that look and behavior?", "qSentId": 878}, {"answer": "In every sense.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 904, "question": "How do you mean?", "qSentId": 903}, {"answer": "Yes, really.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "... does the originality go?", "qSentId": 915}, {"answer": "Oh, you just don't know.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 929, "question": "How is it -- never mind Brad Pitt, who's a bastion of decency, but how have you avoided becoming Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 928}, {"answer": "... a kite right now.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 935, "question": "Ladies?", "qSentId": 934}, {"answer": "Yes, watch out.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 938, "question": "Have we all got a secret Charlie on our hands?", "qSentId": 937}, {"answer": "I'm saying how -- how do you avoid...", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 949, "question": "Are -- are you saying this is me?", "qSentId": 948}, {"answer": "Well, like I said, I think you have to go -- you have to kind of set parameters and -- and one thing I didn't realize, look, first of all, we all signed up for this gig.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 952, "question": "Well, how do you avoid that when it's so obviously available if you want it?", "qSentId": 951}, {"answer": "I've said her before, but Cate Blanchett.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 970, "question": "Who are your -- your idols in the business?", "qSentId": 969}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 975, "question": "You didn't, did you?", "qSentId": 974}, {"answer": "I knew it.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 977, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) on the plane (INAUDIBLE), right?", "qSentId": 976}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 986, "question": "I mean, how can you sleep in a serene way as one who is being a great actor?", "qSentId": 985}, {"answer": "Oh, well, I love Kate Winslet, I love Cameron Diaz, Drew Barrymore.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 994, "question": "ORGAN: What about the actresses?", "qSentId": 993}, {"answer": "I -- well, I think that for a number of reasons.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 998, "question": "Why is it hard in the comedic world?", "qSentId": 997}, {"answer": "Yes, this is my life, people.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1018, "question": "You are lucky, aren't you?", "qSentId": 1017}, {"answer": "I've always had a really big Jimmy Stewart thing.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1022, "question": "Who -- who are your great idols in the film business?", "qSentId": 1021}, {"answer": "No, it's easier in a way cause you -- you know, you have someone who is, you know, kind of captaining the ship.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1030, "question": "Is it harder though to do that?", "qSentId": 1029}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1043, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 1042}, {"answer": "Well, he has already seen them.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1045, "question": "What about your friend's boobs?", "qSentId": 1044}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1047, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 1046}, {"answer": "I tried.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1061, "question": "Did I?", "qSentId": 1060}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1089, "question": "Wendy, will you marry me?", "qSentId": 1088}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1097, "question": "How did this happen?", "qSentId": 1096}, {"answer": "Well, I was -- I mean, it was after -- we started dating actually after the movie wrapped.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1104, "question": "And what was the moment where things sort of got cemented?", "qSentId": 1103}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1110, "question": "Can I be honest with you about something?", "qSentId": 1109}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1113, "question": "Oh, really?", "qSentId": 1112}, {"answer": "It's just so bizarre.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1122, "question": "What is it really like?", "qSentId": 1121}, {"answer": "It's so awkward.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1134, "question": "How can you be with her?", "qSentId": 1133}, {"answer": "I'm pretty sure that's...", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1152, "question": "The rule -- the rule is no tongue?", "qSentId": 1151}, {"answer": "He did.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1161, "question": "Did he -- did he break that rule?", "qSentId": 1160}, {"answer": "I think that was his tactic.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1164, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 1163}, {"answer": "The character would tongue-kiss.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1171, "question": "So you're a serial rule-breaker?", "qSentId": 1170}, {"answer": "No -- yes, she was great about it.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1199, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 1198}, {"answer": "I think when -- when Chris proposed to me.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1224, "question": "Anna, what would you say?", "qSentId": 1223}, {"answer": "Both, actually.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1228, "question": "On or off screen?", "qSentId": 1227}, {"answer": "No way.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1231, "question": "Was he on bended knee like the character?", "qSentId": 1230}, {"answer": "I'll give it to you.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1234, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 1233}, {"answer": "Well, it's just such a tough question.", "docId": "110305pmt", "aSentId": 1241, "question": "Best night of your life?", "qSentId": 1240}]